

CONTACTS



Minsk, Belarus



+375 (25) 780 42 92



yantsevich92@gmail.com



My Portfolio







ABOUT ME

Hello, I am a person who has a strong passion for programming.

I have experience in creating SPA with React/Redux/TypeScript.

Now I am improving my skills in this direction and expanding them with new technologies.

I'm planning to study Node.js, because in the future I see myself as a Full-stack developer.

I spend my leisure time on <u>Codewars</u> or with educational books, and also improving my English.

Open for your suggestions.

SKILLS

- React/Redux
- JavaScript/TypeScript
- Axios/Rest API
- HTML5/CSS3
- Unit Tests/Storybook
- Material UI/Ant Design
- Git

LANGUAGES

- English: A2 (in progress)
- Russian: Native

ANDREY YANTSEVICH

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

Freelance | 01.2021 - Present

- Took part in the creation of a training application.
 Created a registration, login and password recovery form, modal windows, pagination, sorting and filtering, tests, menu and design.
- Created a Todolist application with a login form, as well as with the ability to add, delete, change and filter todolists and tasks.
- Use next developer technologies: React/Redux/Hooks/ReduxThunk/RestAPI/Axios/ Formik/MaterialUI/SCSS, etc.
- Check the correctness of the code with Unit Tests and take Storybook for demonstration of individual modules of the application.
- Use TypeScript for best control of the code in work.
 Fixed bugs related to side effects with using HOCs and Hooks (React.memo, useCallback, useEffect).

Video surveillance system engineer

Minsk Subway | 10.2012 - Present

- Administration and maintenance of the video surveillance systems.
- Assembly, configuration, installation of servers based on Windows Server 2012.
- Support for computer networks.
- Configuring network equipment.
- Skills for working with VMware/VirtualBox virtualization.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

IT-INCUBATOR, 2021

Frontend Developer (React, Redux, JS, TS)

Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics, 2012-2016

Electronic Engineer (Security Systems)